BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 9) 6178/009
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series IX: Industry Code #44, Retail
  - United Retail Employees, 1937-1939 (Box 131, Folder 39)
    - Item 5: Metropolitan Display Mens Association and Window Trimmers and Displatmen's Union of Greater New York, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 144, CIO, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 39)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1938 and expires on 5/1/1939. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
  - United Retail Employees, 1938-1939 (Box 131, Folder 40)
    - Item 1: United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 185, CIO, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 40)
      Agreement effective 10/16/1938 and expires on 10/16/1939. Covers 46 workers in Montevallo, AL
  - United Retail Employees, 1937-1940 (Box 131, Folder 41)
    - Item 1: Retail Dry Goods Employees Union, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 1102, CIO, 1937-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 41)
      Agreement effective 9/14/1937 and expires on 9/14/1940. Covers an unknown number of workers in New York, NY
    - Item 2: Mohican Company and United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 189, CIO, 1937-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 41)
      Agreement effective 11/27/1937 and expires on 9/1/1940. Covers 27 workers in Reading, PA
    - Item 3: Ideal Frocks Inc., Peoples Cooperative, Inc. and United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 201, CIO, 1939-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 41)
      Agreement effective 8/2/1939 and expires on 8/2/1940. Covers 4 workers in Akron, OH
    - Item 4: Rosenbaum Company and United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 101, CIO, Addendum, 1939-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 41)
      Agreement effective 10/9/1939 and expires on 9/1/1940. Covers an unknown number of workers in Pittsburg, PA
  - United Retail Employees, 1939-1940 (Box 131, Folder 42)
    - Item 1: S. Rosenberg and Credit Salesmen and Outside Collectors Union, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 117, CIO, 1939-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 42)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1939 and expires on 11/27/1940. Covers an unknown number of workers in Philadelphia, PA
    - Item 2: Home Baking Co., J. G. McCrory Co. and United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America,Local 152, CIO, 1939-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 42)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1939 and expires on 11/1/1940. Covers 34 workers in Spangler, PA
    - Item 3: Retail Drug Store Employers Union of Greater New York, United Retail and Wholesale Employees of America, Local 1199, CIO, 1939-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 42)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1939 and expires on 10/31/1940. Covers 2000 workers in New York, NY
  - Filling Station Employees, 1936-1939 (Box 131, Folder 43)
    - Item 1: L. L. Coryell Oil Company and Filling Station Employees' Union, Local 18362, 1935-1936; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 43)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1935 and expires on 1/1/1936. Covers 6 workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 2: Filling Station Employees' Union, Local 19570, AFL, Gasoline Station Operators National Council, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 43)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1936 and expires on 5/31/1937. Covers an unknown number of workers in San Francisco, CA
    - Item 3: Goodrich Silvertown Stores and Filling Station Employees' Union, Local 18912, 1936-1937; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 43)
      Agreement effective 6/15/1936 and expires on 6/15/1937. Covers an unknown number of workers in Akron, OH
    - Item 4: The Rubber Institute and Filling Station Employees' Union, Local 19570, AFL, Gasoline Station Operators National Council, 1936-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 43)
      Agreement effective 6/22/1936 and expires on 5/31/1939. Covers 250 workers in San Francisco, CA
    - Item 5: Filling Station, Garage, and Parking Lot Employees' Union, Local 20664, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 43)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1937 and expires on 8/31/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in Philadelphia, PA
    - Item 6: L. L. Coryell Marketing Company and Gasoline Service Station and Warehouse Union, Local 18362, 1938-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 43)
      Agreement effective 3/14/1938 and expires on 5/17/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in St. Louis, MO
  - Federal Labor Unions, before 1940, Retail and Grocery, 1938-1939 (Box 131, Folder 44)
    - Item 1: Goldenson Furniture Company and Furniture Handlers' Union, Federal Labor Union, Local 20407, AFL, 1937-1938; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 44)
      Agreement effective 4/9/1937 and expires on 4/9/1938. Covers an unknown number of workers in Pittsburgh, PA
    - Item 2: Cloquet Merchants Association and Federal Labor Union, Local 20371, AFL, Addendum, 1938-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 44)
      Agreement effective 8/1/1938 and expires on 8/31/1939. Covers an unknown number of workers in Cloquet, MN
    - Item 3: The Firm of the Bartley Company and Wholesale Grocery Employees' Union, AFL, 1939-1939; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 44)
      Agreement effective 6/1/1939 and expires on 12/31/1939. Covers an unknown number of workers in Toledo, OH
  - Butchers and Retail Employees, 1939-1943 (Box 131, Folder 45)
    - Item 1: Morgans Market, Oregon City Safeway Markets, E. Merritz, and others and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 138, AFL, 1937-1941; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 9/20/1937 and expires on 3/31/1941. Covers 37 workers in Oregon City, OR
    - Item 2: Retail Meat Dealers Association and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 73, AFL, 1937-1941; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1937 and expires on 10/1/1941. Covers 1000 workers in Milwaukee, WI
    - Item 3: Frank J. Kuhn Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 424, 1939-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 3/20/1939 and expires on 1/23/1940. Covers an unknown number of workers in Pittsburg, PA
    - Item 4: Appleton Market Mens Retail Association and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 317, 1939-1941; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1939 and expires on 10/1/1941. Covers 100 workers in Appleton, WI
    - Item 5: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 551, AFL, 1939-1940; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 12/3/1939 and expires on 12/3/1940. Covers an unknown number of workers in San Pedro, CA
    - Item 6: Rock Springs, Wyoming Master Butchers and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 205, 1940-1941; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 8/31/1940 and expires on 9/30/1941. Covers 40 workers in Rock Springs, WY
    - Item 7: Schaffner Brothers Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 128, AFL, 1940-1941; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 12/24/1940 and expires on 10/24/1941. Covers an unknown number of workers in Erie, PA
    - Item 8: Oswald and Hess, Fried and Reineman, Denholm's, North Side and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 424, AFL, 1940-1941; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 11/15/1940 and expires on 11/15/1941. Covers an unknown number of workers in Pittsburg, PA
    - Item 9: A and P Tea Company, Safeway Stores and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 302, AFL, 1940-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 11/15/1940 and expires on 1/15/1942. Covers 170 workers in Richmond, VA
    - Item 10: L. H. Payne, Hierschermers Brothers, Schiretts Grocery, and others and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 559, AFL, Illinois State Federation of Labor, Bloomington Federated Trades Assembly, 1940-1941; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 11/15/1940 and expires on 11/15/1941. Covers 40 workers in Bloomington, IL
    - Item 11: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 373, AFL, 1940-1941; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 12/1/1940 and expires on 12/1/1941. Covers 400 workers in Akron, OH
    - Item 12: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 243, AFL, 1940-1941; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 12/1/1940 and expires on 12/1/1941. Covers 78 workers in Jamestown, NY
    - Item 13: Sanitary Grocery Company, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 555, AFL, 1940-1941; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 12/2/1940 and expires on 12/1/1941. Covers 600 workers in Washington, DC
    - Item 14: Super Markets and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 199, AFL, 1940-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 12/12/1940 and expires on 12/12/1942. Covers an unknown number of workers in Wilmington, DE
    - Item 15: Collinsville Merchants and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 449, AFL, 1940-1941; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1940 and expires on 1/1/1941. Covers 22 workers in Collinsville, IL
    - Item 16: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 439, AFL, California State Federation of Labor, Pasadena Central Labor Council, 1941-1941; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1941 and expires on 12/3/1941. Covers 525 workers in Pasadena, CA
    - Item 17: San Diego Fish Company, Star Fisheries, Chesapeake Fish Company, and others and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 229, Western Federation of Butchers of California, 1941-1941; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 1/6/1941 and expires on 12/31/1941. Covers 40 workers in San Diego, CA
    - Item 18: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 81, AFL, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 2/15/1941 and expires on 2/15/1942. Covers 1000 workers in Seattle, WA
    - Item 19: Poultry Producers of California, and others and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 364, Western Federation of Butchers of California, AFL, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 3/1/1941 and expires on 3/1/1942. Covers an unknown number of workers in Petaluma, CA
    - Item 20: Economy Grocery Stores Corporation and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 343, AFL, 1941-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 3/3/1941 and expires on 3/3/1943. Covers 300 workers in Medfield, MA
    - Item 21: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 513, AFL, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 4/4/1941 and expires on 4/4/1942. Covers an unknown number of workers in Birminghman, AL
    - Item 22: St. Paul Retail Meat Guild, National Tea Company, A and P Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 114, AFL, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 4/11/1941 and expires on 4/11/1942. Covers 460 workers in St. Paul, MN
    - Item 23: Green Border Stores, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 431, AFL, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 5/22/1941 and expires on 6/1/1942. Covers an unknown number of workers in Burlington, IA
    - Item 24: First National Stores, Inc. and Mohican Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 328, AFL, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 5/22/1941 and expires on 5/22/1942. Covers 800 workers in Providence, RI
    - Item 25: Central California Retail Meat Dealers Association and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 127, AFL, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 5/27/1941 and expires on 5/27/1942. Covers 125 workers in Stockton, CA
    - Item 26: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 342, AFL, Central Trades and Labor Council, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 6/1/1941 and expires on 6/1/1942. Covers 1950 workers in Brooklyn, NY
    - Item 27: Retail Meat Dealers Association and Fish and Oyster Workers Union, Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 151, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 6/1/1941 and expires on 6/1/1942. Covers 180 workers in Everett, WA
    - Item 28: Kosher Butchers Association and Hebrew Butcher Workers' Union, Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 618, AFL, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 6/1/1941 and expires on 6/1/1942. Covers 105 workers in Dorchester, MA
    - Item 29: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 422, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 6/15/1941 and expires on 6/15/1942. Covers an unknown number of workers in Newark, NJ
    - Item 30: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 551, AFL, Western Federation of Butchers of California, Central Labor Council, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 6/15/1941 and expires on 6/15/1942. Covers an unknown number of workers in San Pedro, CA
    - Item 31: Reusser and Payne and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 70, AFL, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 7/2/1941 and expires on 7/2/1942. Covers an unknown number of workers in Jefferson City, MO
    - Item 32: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 590, AFL, 1941-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 7/16/1941 and expires on 1/2/1943. Covers an unknown number of workers in Pittsburg, PA
    - Item 33: Safeway Stores, Inc., Purity Stores, Ltd., and others and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 364, AFL, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 7/28/1941 and expires on 7/28/1942. Covers 51 workers in Petaluma, CA
    - Item 34: Schwartz Super Market, Schwartz Sanitary Super Market, Harris Market, and others and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 424, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 8/1/1941 and expires on 8/1/1942. Covers 600 workers in Pittsburg, PA
    - Item 35: Diemlers Market and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 70, AFL, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 8/6/1941 and expires on 8/6/1942. Covers an unknown number of workers in Jefferson City, MO
    - Item 36: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 70, AFL, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 8/12/1941 and expires on 8/12/1942. Covers an unknown number of workers in Jefferson City, MO
    - Item 37: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 546, AFL, Illinois Federation of Labor, Chicago Federation of Labor, 1941-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 10/4/1941 and expires on 9/30/1943. Covers an unknown number of workers in Chicago, IL
    - Item 38: Consumers Market, D and B Market, Safeway Stores, and others and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 109, AFL, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1941 and expires on 10/1/1942. Covers 54 workers in Tucson, AR
    - Item 39: Safeway Stores, Inc., Hinky Dinky Grocery and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 548, AFL, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1941 and expires on 10/1/1942. Covers 65 workers in Council Bluffs, IA
    - Item 40: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 551, AFL, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1941 and expires on 1/1/1942. Covers an unknown number of workers in San Pedro, CA
    - Item 41: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 151, AFL, 1941-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1941 and expires on 12/31/1942. Covers an unknown number of workers in Everett, WA
    - Item 42: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 600, AFL, 1941-1941; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1941 and expires on 11/1/1941. Covers 94 workers in Chattanooga, TN
    - Item 43: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 138, AFL, 1941-1941; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1941 and expires on 1/1/1941. Covers 26 workers in Oregon City, OR
    - Item 44: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 151, AFL, 1941-1941; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1941 and expires on 12/31/1941. Covers an unknown number of workers in Everett, WA
    - Item 45: Munns Brothers, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 227, AFL, 1942-1942; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1942 and expires on 12/31/1942. Covers an unknown number of workers in Louisville, KY
    - Item 46: Retail Dealers Assocation and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 561, AFL, Wisconsin Federation of Labor, Superior Federation of Labor, 1942-1934; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 5/1/1942 and expires on 4/30/1934. Covers an unknown number of workers in Superior, WI
    - Item 47: Central California Retail Meat Dealers Association and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 127, AFL, 1942-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 5/31/1942 and expires on 5/31/1943. Covers 98 workers in Stockton, CA
    - Item 48: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 513, AFL, 1942-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 6/13/1942 and expires on 1/1/1943. Covers an unknown number of workers in Birminghman, AL
    - Item 49: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL, Georgia State Federation of Labor, Atlanta Central Labor Union, 1942-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 8/14/1942 and expires on 4/15/1943. Covers an unknown number of workers in Atlanta, GA
    - Item 50: Packing House Workers Union, Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 641, AFL, 1942-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1942 and expires on 8/30/1943. Covers an unknown number of workers
    - Item 51: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 587, 1942-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1942 and expires on 10/1/1943. Covers an unknown number of workers in Coeur d'Alene, ID
    - Item 52: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 528, AFL, 1942-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1942 and expires on 11/30/1943. Covers an unknown number of workers in Dallas, TX
    - Item 53: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 644, AFL, 1942-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1942 and expires on 10/31/1943. Covers an unknown number of workers in Tulsa, OK
    - Item 54: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 92, AFL, 1942-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1942 and expires on 11/1/1943. Covers an unknown number of workers in Oklahoma City, OK
    - Item 55: A and P Tea Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 600, AFL, 1942-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 11/1/1942 and expires on 11/1/1943. Covers an unknown number of workers in Chattanooga, TN
    - Item 56: Kroger Grocery and Baking Company and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 227, AFL, 1942-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 11/2/1942 and expires on 11/2/1943. Covers an unknown number of workers in Louisville, KY
    - Item 57: Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 90, AFL, 1943-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 5/8/1943 and expires on 10/31/1943. Covers an unknown number of workers in Muskogee, OK
    - Item 58: Sipes Self Serving Stores and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, Local 644, AFL, 1943-1943; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 131, Folder 45)
      Agreement effective 5/21/1943 and expires on 10/31/1943. Covers an unknown number of workers in Tulsa, OK
  - Butchers and Retail Employees, 1943-1945 (Box 131, Folder 46)
    Some agreements formerly confidential